Tareva Saunders

Flint, MI • tasaund2@gmail.com • 810.962.3548

OBJECTIVE

Hardworking administrative professional committed to providing a positive experience and environment for customers. Proven success at using various computer software programs, communicating with customers and staff with diverse backgrounds, maintaining customer files, and providing information regarding services.

EDUCATION

Oakland University, Rochester, MI

Degree In Progress

Affiliations: Organizations: American Society for Safety Engineers (President), Association of Black Students (Treasurer), Grizz Gang, Akanke African Dance Troupe (President), and Student to Professional

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Member Solutions Representative

06/2016 to Present

Dort Financial Credit Union, Grand Blanc, MI

- Create and maintain comprehensive job function procedures.
- Streamline procedures to process department invoices.
- Ensuring all files are prepared, processed, and forwarded to attorneys in a timely manner.
- Communicate via phone, email, and mail with members, attorneys, etc.
- Process repossession proceeds, draft and send deficiency letters to members.
- Process court-ordered garnishments/levies and notify members.
- Accounts Receivable: Posting member payments, bankruptcy trustee payments, credit counseling payments, and legal payments.

Receptionist 10/2013 to 05/2016

Trillium Staffing, Flint, MI

- Greet patients in a pleasant manner
- Distribute check-in materials, prepare patient files, and retrieve insurance eligibility.
- Create and maintain client enrollment date.
- Schedule patient appointments and update patient files.
- Copy, scan, and fax, while maintaining the highest degree of confidentiality.

Donor Dialogue Appointment Setter

07/2013 to 10/2013

Dialogue Marketing, Auburn Hills, MI

- Represent clients with a positive and professional image.
- Communicate effectively with clients and staff.
- Handle outgoing and incoming calls to encourage and inspire blood donors.
- Schedule appointments for blood donors.
- Effectively communicate with blood donors about the blood donation process and answer any questions.
- Maintain donor contact information and activity records.

Customer Support Agent

04/2013 to 08/2013

ViSalus Sciences, Troy, MI

- Create a positive experience for customers and promoters.
- Communicate with customers via phone, email, and social media.
- Educate customers and promoters about products and services offered.
- Process customer requests using Microsoft Outlook
- Maintain customer and promoter accounts using Exigo.

Site Administrative Assistant

03/2012 to 03/2013

YouthQuest - After School Enrichment, Flint, MI

- Maintain a safe, organized, and positive learning environment for students.
- Provide direct support to the Site Team Leader
- · Administrative support tasks: Student registration, attendance input, data management, and food services
- Accounting & HR support tasks: Recruitment, staff registration, and payroll.
- Data entry for an additional 10 hours per week remotely.

Administrative Student Assistant

08/2007 to 12/2012

Oakland University - Undergraduate Admissions, Rochester, MI

- Facilitated campus tours for prospective students and family members.
- Presented students and parents with information about university programs and services.

- Communicated positively, via in-person, phone, and email, to prospective students.
- Designed new training procedures and methods for new employees.
- Trained new employees on office protocols and procedures.

SKILLS

Typing Speed: 55 WPM

Skills: Customer Service, Training, Data Entry, Multiple Line Telecommunications, Record Maintenance Procedure Development, Administrative Support,

Technology: Microsoft Office Suite, Oracle Banner Database, EZ Reports, Exigo, Temenos, XP, Cayen, Internet Explorer, Clio,

Pacer, DRM

Soft Skills: Attention to Detail, Problem Solving, Adaptability, Multi-Tasking, Strategic Planning